Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files, 1885-2008 and undated, bulk 1920-1995 RL.00658
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Ford Audiovisual Materials, 1956-2006 and undated [RESTRICTED]
  - Global Business Unit Conferences
    - Tuesday AM session, 2001. TRT: 60:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV43)
    - Venezuela, Andean spot, 1999. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV43)
    - Venezuela, Colombia, 1999. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV43)
    - Venezuela, Mexico, Germany, 2001. TRT: 45:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV43)
    - Youth Presentation, You Can Make It Happen, 1996. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV43)
  - Goodbye, Hello, (English), undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: CD (Box FM-AV43)
  - Granada/T-Bird/Fairmont/Escort, 1976-1982. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV43)
  - Great Car Launch, tape 1, 1998. TRT: 8:30. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV43)
  - Great Car Launch, tape 2, 1998. TRT: 8:30. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV43)
  - Great Jones Productions, Ford 2010, 1998. TRT: 7:57. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV43)
  - Harley Edition (F-Series) images, undated. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV44)
  - Haz lo que quieras...es tu Fiesta, undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV44)
  - Homer Simpson Builds a Car, undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV44)
  - Ideas on Wheels, undated. TRT: 0:30. Format: 16 mm (Box FM-AV44)
  - If campaign (Middle East)
    - Arabic--Master, 1993. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV44)
    - Arabic--Protection master, 1003. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV44)
    - Mustang--Master, 1994. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV44)
    - Mustang--Protection master, 1994. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV44)
    - Mustang Ver--Master, 1993. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV44)
    - Mustang Ver--Protection master, 1993. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV44)
  - India (Sumantra)
    - Ikon, A Car Driven by TTB, 2001. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV44)
  - In Search of 200 MPH, 1987. TRT: 20:50. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV45)
  - International reels (Box FM-AV46)
    - Compilation reel, 1993. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV46)
    - Compilation reel, 1994 first quarter. TRT: 30:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV46)
    - Compilation reel, 1994 second quarter. TRT: 30:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV46)
    - Compilation reel, 1994 third quarter. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV46)
    - Compilation reel, 1994 fourth quarter. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV46)
    - Compilation reel, 1995 first quarter. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV46)
    - Compilation reel, 1995 second quarter. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV47)
    - Compilation reel, 1995 third and fourth quarters. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV47)
    - Compilation reel, tape 1, 1996 Jan.-June. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV47)
    - Compilation reel, tape 2, 1996 Jan.-June. TRT: 30:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV47)
    - Compilation reel, 1996 fourth quarter. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV47)
    - Compilation reel, 1997. TRT: 14:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV47)
    - Compilation reel, 1998 Jan. -June. TRT: 60:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV47)
    - Compilation reel, 2001. TRT: 15:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV47)
    - Compilation reel, 2001 Aug.. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV48)
    - Compilation reel, undated. TRT: 6:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV48)
    - Creative reel: Russia, Chile, Gulf Coast Countries, 1997. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV48)
    - Creative reel conversion, Middle East and Venezuela, 1998. TRT: 17:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV48)
    - Jan.-June TV spots, part I, 1998. TRT: 30:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV48)
    - Jan.-June TV spots, part II, 1998. TRT: 28:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV48)
    - Launch spots, 1997. TRT: 14:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV48)
    - Select reel, 1996. TRT: 17:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV48)
    - Select reel, version 2, 1996. TRT: 12:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV48)
  - Japan (Tokyo) (Box FM-AV49)
    - 1996 Model TV commercial in Japan, 1995. TRT: 6:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV49)
    - 1996 Model TV commercial reel, tape 1, 1995. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV49)
    - 1996 Model TV commercial reel, tape 2, 1995. TRT: 6:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV49)
    - Focus 1.6/2.0, Outfitters, Escape, undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV49)
    - Focus, Outfitters, Escape (Chophouse), 2000. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV49)
    - Ford USA Brand video (Japanese narration), undated. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV49)
    - Ford of Japan presentation, rough cut, 1995. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV49)
    - Galaxy TVCF, undated. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV49)
    - Historical reel, 1990-1995. TRT: 7:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV49)
    - New Explorer TV CF, 1995. TRT: 2:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV49)
    - Quarterly reel, 1996. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV49)
    - RHD Taurus TVC reel, 1996. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV50)
    - Taurus promtional, client approved version, 1996. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV50)
    - Taurus promotional, rough cut, 1996. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV50)
    - Telstar wagon, 1997. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV50)
    - Terminator II, undated. TRT: 15:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV50)
    - TV Commercial reel, 1995. TRT: 15:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV50)
    - TV Commercial reel, 1996. TRT: 8:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV50)
  - Korea (Seoul)
    - Taurus (performance, safety), Mystique, 1998. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV50)
    - Taurus TVC, 1997. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV50)
  - Latin American compilation, 1998. TRT: 15:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV50)
  - Latin American reel, 1998-1999. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV50)
  - Lincoln Ad Planner, 2001. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV50)
  - Lincoln-Mercury Running Footage, 1996. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV50)
  - Main Street Multimedia, Can You Dig It?, 1997. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV50)
  - Majors, Jeson, New Man From Thunder Road (Bill Elliott), 1988. TRT: 23:40. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV51)
  - Malaysia (Kuala Lumpur) (Box FM-AV52)
    - Animal Farm 3/2/1, 1999. TRT: 6:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV52)
    - Assorted TVC's in English and Malay, tape 1, 2000. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV52)
    - Assorted TVC's in English and Malay, tape 2, 2000. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV52)
    - Competitive reel, 2000. TRT: 6:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV52)
    - Ranger, Make Your Own Road, 2000. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV52)
    - Ranger, Ranger World and Make Your Own Road, 2000. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV52)
  - Mambo Clearance music splits, 2001. TRT: 6:00. Format: Audiocassette (Box FM-AV52)
  - Mike Matheson, talks at the speed of sound, voiceover demo, undated. TRT: 15:00. Format: CD (Box FM-AV52)
  - Maverick YUP, circa 1970. TRT: 1:00. Format: 16 mm (Box FM-AV52)
  - McGarvey, Tim, demo, undated. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV52)
  - Mercury Ad Planner, 2001. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV52)
  - Mexico
    - 12 TVC's, 2000. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV52)
    - Assorted TVC's, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV52)
    - Campaign, 1995. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV52)
    - Campaign, 1999. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV53)
    - Compilation reel, 1997. TRT: 21:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV53)
    - Compilation reel, 2001. TRT: 30:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV53)
    - Escort, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV53)
    - Explorer, undated. TRT: 2:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV53)
    - Explorer Offroader, 2001. TRT: 1:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV53)
    - Fiesta, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV53)
    - Fiesta TV Launch,. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV53)
    - Focus and KA, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV53)
    - F-Series, undated. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV53)
    - Macroventa Monstruo, undated. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV54)
    - Mystique, undated. TRT: 4:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV54)
    - Sable and Contour, 1995. TRT: 4:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV54)
    - Trucks, Escape, 2001. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV54)
    - Work copies for 1996 launch, 1995. TRT: 8:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV54)
    - Various, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV54)
    - Various, 2001. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV54)
  - NAAO export (Middle East), Mercury/Ford, 1993. TRT: 4:00. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV54)
  - National Speed Stks, Metro Detroit Ford Dealers, undated. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV54)
  - Mustang Coupe, It Was It Is, 1993. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV54)
  - New Zealand (Auckland)
    - 10 commercials, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV54)
    - All Blacks rugby sponsorship, 1999. TRT: 4:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV54)
    - Compilation reel, tape 1, 1996. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
    - Compilation reel, tape 2, 1996. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
    - Compilation reel, 1997. TRT: 7:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
    - Compilation reel, tape 1, 1999-2000. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
    - Compilation reel, tape 2, 1999-2000. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
    - Compilation reel, 2001. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
    - Compile, 1997. TRT: 6:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
    - Escape, Explorer, 2001. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
    - Ford Report, circa 1993. TRT: 12:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV55)
    - Ford TVC's, undated. TRT: 4:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV55)
    - Rugby sponsorship analysis, 1997. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
    - True Blue FDAF campaign, 2000. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV55)
  - No Boundaries
    - Escape, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV55)
    - Escape artwork, undated. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV55)
    - Experience it like never before (Explorer), 2002. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV55)
    - Ford Outfitters, 2000. TRT: 13:00. Format: DVD, 3 copies (Box FM-AV56)
    - Ford Outfitters (Chophouse), undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV56)
    - Samples from New Zealand, Malaysia, 2001. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV56)
    - Samples from New Zealand, Malaysia, 2001. TRT: 2:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV56)
  - OFS (Oakland Family Services) Hollywood booklet, 1999. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV56)
  - Ogilvy & Mather (Ford of Europe)
    - Escort Atlanta Spain, 1997. TRT: 1:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV56)
    - Escort compilation, tape 1, 1997. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV56)
    - Escort compilation, tape 2, 1997. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV56)
    - Escort compilation (Britain), 1997. TRT: 6:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV56)
    - FDAA examples, 1999. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV56)
    - Fiesta and Escort advertising, 1994. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV56)
    - Fiesta Caramelo (Spain), tape 1, undated. TRT: 1:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV56)
    - Fiesta Caramelo (Spain), tape 2, undated. TRT: 2:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV57)
    - Fiesta Features campaign, 1997. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV57)
    - Fiesta Features campaign central, 1997. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV57)
    - Fiesta It's Alive launch and follow up, 1996. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV57)
    - Focus on Ford, 1997. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV57)
    - Ford Customer Service spots, 1995. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV57)
    - KA promotion, 1997. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV57)
    - Mondeo Control/Senses, 1997. TRT: 3:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV57)
    - Mondeo Nicholas, Granada, Fiesta, Escort, 1994. TRT: 7:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV57)
    - Mondeo Spain Control, 1999. TRT: 1:30. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV57)
    - Mondeo X-Factor/Saloon, 1997. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV57)
    - Ranger, undated. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV57)
    - Simplicity Bridges/Connect, 1999. TRT: 4:30. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV57)
    - Taurus/Sable, 1997. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV58)
  - Our Town campaign, 1998. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV58)
  - Peru (Lima)
    - Contour Lanzamiento, 1995. TRT: 20:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV58)
    - Ranger Ride and Drive, 1997. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV58)
    - Ranger Ride and Drive, 1997. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV58)
  - Pickup proofs, 1999. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV58)
  - Piliouras, George, Ford spots, 2003. TRT: 6:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV58)
  - Preston, Mark, demo, undated. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV58)
  - Promo film (Granada, etc.), 1981. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV58)
  - Puerto Rico (San Juan) (Box FM-AV59)
    - 32 spots, 1995. TRT: 16:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV59)
    - Alguna duda, 1999. TRT: 1:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV59)
    - Anthem (Revisited), undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV59)
    - Branding, undated. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV59)
    - Branding, 1998. TRT: 1:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV59)
    - Compilation reel, 2000. TRT: 10:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV59)
    - Corporate/Dealers, 1999. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV59)
    - Corporate/Explorer, 1995. TRT: 2:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV59)
    - Corporate/FDAF, 1997. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV59)
    - El Gran Evento del Porciento, 1997. TRT: 0:30. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV59)
    - Escort, undated. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV59)
    - Explorer 2002, 2001. TRT: 0:30. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV59)
    - Explorer/Ranger, undated. TRT: 0:30. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV60)
    - F-150 Titanic, 1996. TRT: 0:30. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV60)
    - Focus spots/Taurus spots/Firestone. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV60)
    - Ford Dealers, Stress Escape/Se Busca, 2001. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV60)
    - Geyser, 2001. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV60)
    - Outfitters, Sin Fronteras, 2000. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV60)
    - Ranger, undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV60)
    - Ranger/Red Carpet/Escort/Brand, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV60)
    - Se mueve con tigo/Branding, 1998. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV60)
    - Taurus, 1995. TRT: 0:30. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV60)
    - Toyota Corolla and Ford Focus, 1998. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV60)
    - Toyota Corolla and Ford Focus brand animatics, circa 1998. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV60)
    - Various spots, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV60)
    - Various TVC's (P.R. reel), 1997-1998. TRT: 20:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV60)
    - Various TVC's (Focus, Taurus, Firestone), (Chophouse), undated. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS, 2 reels (Box FM-AV61)
  - Quality…A Way of Life, 1992
    - 1903-1927. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV61)
    - 1927-1942. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV61)
    - 1942-1965. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV61)
  - Race art, 2002. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV61)
  - Racing headshots, 2004. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV61)
  - Radio spots, from Winfield Taylor, tape 1, circa 1956. TRT: 15:00. Format: 1/4 audio tape (Box FM-AV61)
  - Radio spots, from Winfield Taylor, tape 2, circa 1956. TRT: 15:00. Format: 1/4 audio tape (Box FM-AV61)
  - Ranger
    - CGI final, 2003. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV61)
    - Edge, 2003. Format: CD-R, 2 discs (Box FM-AV61)
    - Miscellaneous images, 1999. Format: CD-R, 2 discs (Box FM-AV61)
  - Russell, Tony (voice-over demos)
    - An Ass-Pocket Full of Whiskey, 2003. TRT: 11:00. Format: CD (Box FM-AV61)
    - Speak of the Devil, 2001. TRT: 13:00. Format: CD (Box FM-AV61)
  - Russia (Moscow)
    - Competitors' reel, 1997. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV61)
    - Escort, 1998. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV61)
    - Escort, 1998. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS-PAL (Box FM-AV61)
    - Looped video (Taurus, Heritage), undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV61)
    - Moscow Motorshow, tape 1, 1996. TRT: 1:30. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV61)
    - Moscow Motorshow, tape 2, 1996. TRT: 1:30. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV61)
    - Untitled, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV61)
  - Saturday Night Live spoof commercials, undated. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV62)
  - Schroer Master A/B/C, undated. TRT: 60:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV62)
  - Selected Ford Communications Network news stories, undated. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV62)
  - Serling Desert revision, undated. TRT: 1:00. Format: 16mm (Box FM-AV62)
  - South Africa (Johannesburg)
    - Abridged show reel, 2001. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV62)
    - Compilation reel, 1998. TRT: 13:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV62)
    - Compilation for Detroit,. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV62)
    - Fiesta/Mondeo/T-Bird/Brand and Focus, 1999. TRT: 15:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV62)
    - Focus Kitenga animatic, undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV62)
    - Laser phase-out, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV62)
    - Quarterly package, 1995. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS-PAL (Box FM-AV62)
    - Ranger promotional, Sub-Saharan edits, 1999. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS-PAL (Box FM-AV62)
    - Tracer/Falcon/Explorer/Built Ford Tough, 1997. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV62)
    - Tracer/Falcon/Explorer/Built Ford Tough, 1997. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS-PAL (Box FM-AV62)
  - Sports music clip, Show No Mercy, 1997. TRT: 6:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV62)
  - Sub Zero presents Superblend, undated. TRT: 63:00. Format: CD (Box FM-AV62)
  - Supercrew Fire Crew/Welcome to the Garage, 2000. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV62)
  - Taiwan (Taipei)
    - Brand/Tierra/Mondeo/Liata/Festiva, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV62)
    - Carmakers advertising compilation, 1999. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV63)
    - Competitive advertisements, 1988. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV63)
    - Compilation reel, undated. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV63)
    - Corporate Teaser, undated. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV63)
    - Creative, 1996. TRT: 60:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV63)
    - Escape A copy, 2000. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV63)
    - Escape X, undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV63)
    - Festiva/Liata/Mondeo/Corporate/Retail, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV63)
    - Festiva/Tierra/Mondeo/Truck, 1999. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV63)
    - Ford advertising reel, 1999. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV63)
    - Ford Lio Ho commercials, 1995. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV63)
    - Ford TVC's, undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV63)
    - Grand Festiva, 1998. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Historical reel, 1990-1995. TRT: 60:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV64)
    - Liata/Christening, 1998. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV64)
    - Liata/Christening, 1998. TRT: 5:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV64)
    - Liata Four Weddings and a Liata, undated. TRT: 2:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Liata Love in the Fast Lane, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV64)
    - Liata Love in the Fast Lane, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV64)
    - Liata/Mondeo/Festiva, undated. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Liata TVC, 1998. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Liata TVC, 1998. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Mazda Taiwan,. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Metrostar teaser/Thematic/Tierra LS, undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Mondeo, undated. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Mondeo engine safety, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Mondeo launch campaign, 1998. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV64)
    - Mondeo/Tierra/Truck launch, 1999. TRT: 5:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV65)
    - Mondeo TVC, undated. TRT: 1:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV65)
    - Mondeo work review, 1999. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV65)
    - Moving with You, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV65)
    - Moving with You, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV65)
    - New Telstar/Liata/Ford Today/Retail, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV65)
    - Primary brand/Tierra/New Liata retail campaign, 1998. TRT: 30:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV65)
    - Pronto TVC's. 1998. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV65)
    - Quarterly reel, undated. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV65)
    - Retail Jan.-May, 1998. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV65)
    - Tierra Holding Hands, undated. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (NTSC) (Box FM-AV65)
    - Tierra/Tierra Life/Mondeo RS, undated. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV65)
    - Windstar, 1998. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV65)
  - Taurus and the Pursuit of Excellence, 1986. TRT: 15:35. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV65)
  - Taurus images, 1998-2000 and undated. Format: CD-R, 8 discs (Box FM-AV65)
  - Taurus Moonroof/Great Outdoors, (Chophouse), undated. TRT: 6:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV66)
  - Taurus Product Advantage Tour, 2001. TRT: 15:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV66)
  - Taurus Trust, 1993. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV66)
  - Taurus Trust (with Explorer), 1993. TRT: 1:00. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV66)
  - Television Spots That Work Hard For Our Clients, (Chophouse), undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV66)
  - Tempo Galadari, 1992. TRT: 0:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV66)
  - Tempo/Topaz commercials, 1992. TRT: 1:30. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV66)
  - Tempo/Topaz revisions, 1993. TRT: 3:00. Format: 1" video (Box FM-AV66)
  - Thailand (Bangkok)
    - Aspire, undated. TRT: 2:00. Format: NTSC (Box FM-AV66)
    - Aspire, undated. TRT: 0:15. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV67)
    - Aspire, Mondial, 1995. TRT: 4:00. Format: PAL (Box FM-AV67)
    - Competitive--Cars, 2000. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
    - Competitive--Luxury cars, 2000. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
    - Competitive--Pickups, 2000. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
    - Footage J97, 2000. TRT: 110:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV67)
    - Global re-positioning, Field of Jade, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
    - Global re-positioning, Reflection of a Smile, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
    - Historical reel, 2000. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
    - Laser, 1999. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS-NTSC (Box FM-AV67)
    - Ranger launch, 1998. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
    - Ranger learning video, 1998. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
    - Ranger pre-launch, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
    - TVC's, 1998-1999. TRT: 30:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV67)
  - Think Ford First, undated. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV67)
  - Thunderbird billboard, 2003. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV67)
  - Timeless Stories, 1998. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV68)
  - Trucks
    - Built Ford Tough/Superduty/Expedition, 2002. Format: CD-R (Box FM-AV68)
    - Truck Season Ad Planner, 1998. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV68)
    - Twin Cities FDAF, F-Series promotion, 1995. TRT: 8:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV68)
  - Turkey (Istanbul)
    - Cargo, undated. TRT: 2:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV68)
    - Cargo, undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV68)
    - Cargo, Asiklar, undated. TRT: 4:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV69)
    - Escort spots, 1997. TRT: 4:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV69)
    - Ford Facts and Ford Transit, undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV69)
    - Ghia/Anatolie/North Anatolie, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV69)
    - Mondeo, undated. TRT: 5:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV69)
    - Mondeo, undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV69)
    - Presentation, 1998. TRT: 15:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV69)
    - Rally, undated. TRT: 3:00. Format: NTSC (Box FM-AV69)
    - Show Must Go On, 1997. TRT: 3:00. Format: PAL (Box FM-AV69)
    - Showreel, 1996. TRT: 3:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV69)
    - Showreel, undated. TRT: 10:00. Format: VHS (Box FM-AV69)
    - Transit, 1997. TRT: 3:00. Format: Betacam SP (Box FM-AV69)
    - Transit, 2000. TRT: 4:00. Format: VHS-PAL (Box FM-AV69)
    - Transit 4 TVC's, 1996. TRT: 4:00. Format: Umatic (Box FM-AV69)
  - United Kingdom (London)